

ABOUT ME

I have been learning crayon drawing since I was 5 years old and watercolor painting since I was 10 years old until now. I am very confident about my watercolor works.

I like drawing and designing very much, and I know that there will always be someone better than me. I hope to work in the art industry and keep learning new things, gaining more experience and technical skills so that I can do better in this field.

LANGUAGES







CHINESE

HOBBIES







PHOTOGRAPHY

CONTACT INFO



017-7583911



weijietan90@gmail.com



Gemas, Negeri Sembilan

TAN WEI JIE

Bachelor of Design with Honours

I am a gaming design student at UPSI. In these 4 years of practice, I have mastered Unity, Blender, Al, PS, PR and some other common design adobe software with certain knowledge.



WORK EXPERIENCE

Buddhist Association

Jan 2016 - Mac 2017

Volunteer at the Buddhist Society to teach children every Saturday while waiting for the SPM results

Yu Lee Florist

Jan 2019 - Jul 2019

I learned at a florist and worked as a waiter and cashier for 7 months while waiting for university admission.



EDUCATION

Sekolah Menengah Kebangsaan Gemas

2012-2016

SPM

BM (C+), BI (D), P.Moral (B+), Sejarah (B), Maths (A), P.Seni (B+), AddMaths (C+), Physics (D), Chemistry (E), Biology (E), BC (A-)

Sekolah Menengah Kebangsaan Tuanku Abdul Rahman

STPM (CGPA 2.83)

2017-2018

Pengajian Am (A-), Geografi (B), Ekonomi (C+), Pengajian Perniagaan (C+)

Universiti Pendidikan Sultan Idris (UPSI)

2019 - 2023

DFGRFF

Bachelor of Design (Digital Games) with Honours (AC33)

SOFTWARE

SKILLS

Game Design

Drowing Graphic Design **Painting**









